Hey, when is the
shooting time?
Hey, eat food 100 times.
Just want to satisfy your stomach or not? First eat and
drink.
Hey, at 1 o'clock,
shooting is at 1:30, food is the first thing that needs to be done.
[laughs]
Hey, the shooting of the film is going on. Call the food distribution and go quickly.
Call it. Hey,
go quickly. You have brought the film
star hungry and hungry. You have made the film star
sleep. First make it a flop and then leave it.
Sir, it is taking
so much time.
Hey, sir,
no one becomes a star by wearing glasses.
[laughs] And a man
's [laughs] And a man's
[laughs]
And a man's [laughs]
Where are you?
Start shooting and make it
quickly.
Okay [laughs]
No, the
glasses are off.
Yes, come out quickly.
But
okay,
sir, the camera is ready, ready, should
I put it on?
Hey, how are you doing?
[laughs] I do
n't eat food. Due to
habit, sir, I am forced to chew work. It is a bitter
thing.
[laughs]
Hey, not in that, not in me. The
camera is in that. I
sit quietly and cut the chicken.
[laughter] If you want to
know
then see
[laughter]
okay it's as per your wish
ok what do you think about the heroine
hey heroine
[music]
where should I go rekha after falling [music]
so where should I go after falling to pieces
hey sir
look what will I do after falling to pieces [laughter]
[screaming sound]
ok ok do your work
[laughter]
heroine
sir come what do you do
sir practice here then do a film
good I like it come
no
[music]
a hero should ask a heroine somewhere yes yes what is the
dialogue hey smart brother you have come
oh no come ok do one work go and bring it like this you
know you are very famous [laughter]
yes so hero and heroine so I will take you to my home
world
quickly heroine yes ok sir ok I will
give the cameraman ready yes sir ready sir
heroine ready ready sir
hero is ready moh
also ready
action
me then in this
[music]
quickly quote ahead hey there are
few dialogues hey then where should I say heroine
's home world kechchi
hey sirchi tochi
ka mahi sir  Yes, I am
sitting, go quickly apply flour powder
[laughs]
okay okay
just do
crow biryani in front and behind, do your work son, respect the hero, it
looked good, no no no,
hey makeup artist, how much time did it take,
sir, sir, do your work, just a minute in
English [laughs] okay okay,
hurry up, hurry up,
sir, makeup is done
okay okay, go quickly, go away from the people, go
quickly
[music]
cameraman,
why are you ready
hey guys, cut cut, Kartik Aryan failed
hey father, I am
behind, then
turn around
hey learn from my darling, hey
properly
hey sir, double sir,
double yes,
extra expenses, expenses,
household expenses
[laughter]
see the shooting of half the case [laughter]
see the shooting, turn on the light, you go turn on the light, okay, it's a
star
[laughter]
everything is ready, yes everything is ready, yes action
sir, cut cut cut, hit the face light, hit the face light
[laughter]
oh my god, no
light, no second light,
come
[music] for the
line of light,
go to the bathroom
[laughter]
second light, no, it's a
dibri, it's a dibri,
candle  It would have been better if you had brought it, wrist
clay dibri
[laughs]
without light connection
oh my face is not in my mouth,
I can't even eat without an apple
oh emotions with
love
okay so
without even a moment
oh so much laughter listen to the story, listen to the camera,
listen to the voice of my heart and
said loudly,
hey director sahab, which hero,
tell me, you should have done better than one, do it in
action, in action, hold the camera in action, play the role of X, do
n't joke, you are talking seriously, oh my god, you have
made my life hell,
for whom did you come friend wow wow wow, what a
dialogue, super super,
where did you learn that dialogue,
cameraman, take this shot,
yes show me the whole one, later get the next shot done,
yes okay, do
n't hit me in the chest
[music]
I can't stay without tea even for a moment,
director sahab, I am
hungry after drinking tea,
first have tea and breakfast
sir, tea
special, spicy chamcham chamachi with
sugar, oh
I would die.  [Music]
[Laughter]
Look, don't you look, hey, you have to get out
of the shooting with your tongue, throw him out
of the world too, you
old lady [screaming]
[Laughter]
Release your dialogue, talk to yourself,
yes, okay, okay,
hey sir, you keep taking punches at the heroine, from
where do you want to, pick up whatever you want, your
film would have become a superhit,
okay, if you bring whatever you want, it's like the
line of a covered tapori, you bastard [Laughter] then the film is
not a superhit, Golu, it's not
okay,
hey [Laughter]
in the film, but the hero is your hero
[Laughter]
stop, you understand, hey, hey, wait, wait,
wait, then
later I wo
n't even eat paan, but [Laughter]
okay, then give me a good suit, it's of
no use, concentrate on your work, start quickly,
start quickly, yes, everything is ready, yes, Cameraman,
yes, cameraman, and cameraman, don't
look at me like a work swindler [Laughter]
Cameraman, don't
become a hero, go quickly, I will shoot, finish the film, so there is a
scene of a hero playing the guitar, where does he
leave and impersonate,
hey  So did you play the guitar or not, don't you know?
Yes sir, yes I know, oh, tribals are not
playing dholki or mandar, okay, okay, okay, okay, yes, yes, okay, okay, ready
[screaming] hey, my love, what a kill, okay [laughs]
wow, what are you saying, super, too, tongue, oh my god
[laughs]
fantastic,
okay, do it today, the shooting will be over, pack up, you will feel like a
family man, and
I will get everyone's number on Google, then I will get the
money,
director sahab and
[screaming] hey,
cameraman, where are you,
come quickly,
where is the shooting, I am not in the mood for
shooting, bata fish,
bata kata fish, bone bone, show the
clip, show the clip, it is
super, we will earn money from the film,
hey
[laughs]
hey, director sir,
where are you, where is the
problem, what's the problem
[laughter],
memory, see,
how are you, it's
not a suit
[laughs]
hey
[laughter]